Guide to the Stuart Elliott papers, 1875-2014 and undated RL.11108
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Writings File, 1969-2014 and undated; 7
  - 2011, 6
    - 2/11--Advertising Research Foundation 75th anniversary, 2011 (Box 109, Folder 11)
    - 2/12--Super Bowl/Groupon, 2011 (Box 109, Folder 12)
    - 2/17--Chobani, 2011 (Box 109, Folder 13)
    - 2/17--John Slattery (Mad Men)/Same-sex marriage, 2011 (Box 109, Folder 14)
    - 2/17--Old Nayy, 2011 (Box 109, Folder 15)
    - 2/17--Plenty of Fish, 2011 (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - 2/18--E! Red Carpet, 2011 (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - 2/22--Chicco, 2011 (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - 2/22--Southern Comfort, 2011 (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - 2/24--Academy Awards (Oscars), 2011 (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - 2/25--Ford, 2011 (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - 2/28--Macy's, 2011 (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - 2/28--MDC Partners, 2011 (Box 110, Folder 8)
    - 3/1--Oscars ad review, 2011 (Box 110, Folder 9)
    - 3/4--Chain restaurants, 2011 (Box 110, Folder 10)
    - 3/7--Royal Caribbean, 2011 (Box 110, Folder 11)
    - 3/7--Starbucks, 2011 (Box 110, Folder 12)
    - 3/7--Tuna the Wonderful campaign, 2011 (Box 110, Folder 13)
    - 3/8--FTC and alcohol ads, 2011 (Box 110, Folder 14)
    - 3/8--Skins (series) ad sponsors, 2011 (Box 110, Folder 15)
    - 3/9--72 and Sunny (agency), 2011 (Box 110, Folder 16)
    - 3/9--Lipman, 2011 (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - 3/9--Mighty Mutt, 2011 (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - 3/10--Shorty's, 2011 (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - 3/11--Hilton, 2011 (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - 3/11--Volvo/YouTube, 2011 (Box 111, Folder 5)
    - 3/11--World Water Week, 2011 (Box 111, Folder 6)
    - 3/14--Battle for Bean Street, 2011 (Box 111, Folder 7)
    - 3/14--March Madness, 2011 (Box 111, Folder 8)
    - 3/16--AFLAC/Chrysler social media, 2011 (Box 111, Folder 9)
    - 3/16--Partners Napier, 2011 (Box 111, Folder 10)
    - 3/17--Kantar ad spending, 2011 (Box 111, Folder 11)
    - 3/18--Burger King, 2011 (Box 111, Folder 12)
    - 3/18--Jenn-Aire, 2011 (Box 111, Folder 13)
    - 3/18--Memory Lane, 2011 (Box 111, Folder 14)
    - 3/18--Sears, 2011 (Box 111, Folder 15)
    - 3/21--Bravo (television), 2011 (Box 111, Folder 16)
    - 3/21--Horizon Milk, 2011 (Box 111, Folder 17)
    - 3/22--AFLAC, 2011 (Box 112, Folder 1)
    - 3/22--AT, 2011 (Box 112, Folder 2)
    - 3/22--VW/Skins (series), 2011 (Box 112, Folder 3)
    - 3/23--MTV/Skins (series), 2011 (Box 112, Folder 4)
    - 3/25--Campbell Mithun/Twitter, 2011 (Box 112, Folder 5)
    - 3/28--Telemundo/Spanish TV, 2011 (Box 112, Folder 6)
    - 3/29--Spike TV, 2011 (Box 112, Folder 7)
    - 3/30--InterPublic, 2011 (Box 112, Folder 8)
    - 3/31--Major League Baseball, 2011 (Box 112, Folder 9)
    - 4/1--Fox Hispanic, 2011 (Box 112, Folder 10)
    - 4/4--Fanta, 2011 (Box 112, Folder 11)
    - 4/5--Hispanic market, 2011 (Box 112, Folder 12)
    - 4/5--NBCUniversal upfront, 2011 (Box 112, Folder 13)
    - 4/6--AFLAC duck, 2011 (Box 112, Folder 14)
    - 4/6--Ovation Channel, 2011 (Box 112, Folder 15)
    - 4/7--L'Eggs, 2011 (Box 112, Folder 16)
    - 4/8--Gap, 2011 (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - 4/10--Frito-Lay, 2011 (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - 4/11--Adweek, 2011 (Box 113, Folder 3)
    - 4/11--Maxwell House/Passover, 2011 (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - 4/12--Hot Wheels, 2011 (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - 4/13--Kraft/Ghost brands, 2011 (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - 4/13--Scripps upfront, 2011 (Box 113, Folder 7)
    - 4/14--Advertising industry and job market, 2011 (Box 113, Folder 8)
    - 4/14--CBS greenwashing, 2011 (Box 113, Folder 9)
    - 4/14--Morgan Spurlock, 2011 (Box 113, Folder 10)
    - 4/15--ESPN/MasterCard/Soccer, 2011 (Box 113, Folder 11)
    - 4/18--Evian Babies, 2011 (Box 113, Folder 12)
    - 4/18--United Methodist Church/Malaria, 2011 (Box 113, Folder 13)
    - 4/18--VW Beetle, 2011 (Box 113, Folder 14)
    - 4/19--Acura/Thor (movie), 2011 (Box 113, Folder 15)
    - 4/19--Agency entrepreneurship, 2011 (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - 4/19--Pulitzer, 2011 (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - 4/20--Checkout coupons, 2011 (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - 4/21--Luke Sullivan/SCAD, 2011 (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - 4/22--Pom Wonderful Presents the Greatest Movie Ever Sold, 2011 (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - 4/25--Aspen/Epsilon, 2011 (Box 114, Folder 6)
    - 4/25--Cheerwine, 2011 (Box 114, Folder 7)
    - 4/27--AFLAC, 2011 (Box 114, Folder 8)
    - 4/28--Royal wedding, 2011; 2 folders (Box 114, Folder 9-10)
    - 4/29--BP oil spill, 2011 (Box 114, Folder 11)
    - 4/29--Ford "Drive one" campaign, 2011 (Box 114, Folder 12)
    - 4/29--Royal wedding, 2011 (Box 115, Folder 1)
    - 4/29--Teleflora, 2011 (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - 5/1--Upfronts, 2011 (Box 115, Folder 3)
    - 5/2--Tillamook, 2011 (Box 115, Folder 3a)
    - 5/3--USA upfront, 2011 (Box 115, Folder 4)
    - 5/3--Westin Hotels, 2011 (Box 115, Folder 5)
    - 5/5--Coca-Cola 125th anniversary, 2011 (Box 115, Folder 6)
    - 5/5--HopStop/Equinox, 2011 (Box 115, Folder 7)
    - 5/5--Tupperware, 2011 (Box 115, Folder 8)
    - 5/9--North of Nine, 2011 (Box 115, Folder 9)
    - 5/9--N.Y. Lottery, 2011 (Box 115, Folder 10)
    - 5/9--R/GA, 2011 (Box 115, Folder 11)
    - 5/10--Canadian Club, 2011 (Box 115, Folder 12)
    - 5/10--Red Baron Pizza, 2011 (Box 115, Folder 13)
    - 5/12--UBS Billboard, 2011 (Box 115, Folder 14)
    - 5/16--Central Park Conservancy, 2011 (Box 115, Folder 15)
    - 5/16--NBC upfront, 2011 (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - 5/16--Upfronts, 2011; 4 folders (Box 116, Folder 2-5)
    - 5/17--Hispanic TV, 2011 (Box 116, Folder 6)
    - 5/17--Upfronts, 2011; 2 folders (Box 116, Folder 7-8)
    - 5/18--Upfronts, 2011 (Box 116, Folder 9)
    - 5/19--Upfronts, 2011; 2 folders (Box 116, Folder 10-11)
    - 5/19--Upfronts, 2011 (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - 5/20--Upfronts, 2011 (Box 117, Folder 2)
    - 5/23--BrandCenter, 2011 (Box 117, Folder 3)
    - 5/23--JetBlue, 2011 (Box 117, Folder 4)
    - 5/23--Sears, 2011 (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - 5/23--Upfront recap, 2011 (Box 117, Folder 6)
    - 5/23--YouTube, 2011 (Box 117, Folder 7)
    - 5/25--U.S. Army, 2011 (Box 117, Folder 8)
    - 5/26--Heineken, 2011 (Box 117, Folder 9)
    - 5/26--Mr. Youth/San Francisco, 2011 (Box 117, Folder 10)
    - 5/26--NeuroFocus, 2011 (Box 117, Folder 11)
    - 5/27--Sam Adams/Dickson Farmstands Meat, 2011 (Box 117, Folder 12)
    - 5/31--Tourism Montreal, 2011 (Box 117, Folder 13)
    - 6/6--Mars Candy, 2011 (Box 117, Folder 14)
    - 6/7--Made in New York, 2011 (Box 117, Folder 15)
    - 6/7--Upfront spending, 2011 (Box 117, Folder 16)
    - 6/8--Ian Schrager, 2011 (Box 117, Folder 17)
    - 6/9--Glee/Bing, 2011 (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - 6/9--Upfront, 2011 (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - 6/10--State Farm, 2011 (Box 118, Folder 3)
    - 6/10--Taco Bell, 2011 (Box 118, Folder 4)
    - 6/13--Coalition of Innovative Media Measurement (CIMM), 2011 (Box 118, Folder 5)
    - 6/13--Era detergent, 2011 (Box 118, Folder 6)
    - 6/13--Kantar Media, 2011 (Box 118, Folder 7)
    - 6/14--PriceWaterhouseCoopers, 2011 (Box 118, Folder 8)
    - 6/15--E! Network, 2011 (Box 118, Folder 9)
    - 6/15--GolinHarris, 2011 (Box 118, Folder 10)
    - 6/15--HSBC/Wimbledon, 2011 (Box 118, Folder 11)
    - 6/15--Weiden Kennedy "Shop", 2011 (Box 118, Folder 12)
    - 6/16--Kia Super Bowl, 2011 (Box 118, Folder 13)
    - 6/16--Woolite/Rob Zombie, 2011 (Box 118, Folder 14)
    - 6/17--House Party/Redbook Happy Hour, 2011 (Box 118, Folder 15)
    - 6/20--Bravo "Summer Camp" campaign, 2011 (Box 118, Folder 16)
    - 6/20--Planters/Peanut Butter Doug, 2011 (Box 119, Folder 1)
    - 6/21--Chevrolet/Super Bowl, 2011 (Box 119, Folder 2)
    - 6/22--Banana Republic/Mad Men, 2011 (Box 119, Folder 3)
    - 6/22--Pump Room, 2011 (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - 6/22--Sabra, 2011 (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - 6/23--Mentos gum, 2011 (Box 119, Folder 6)
    - 6/24--IFC/The Big C, 2011 (Box 119, Folder 7)
    - 6/27--Hearst Publications, 2011 (Box 119, Folder 8)
    - 6/27--Honey Nut Cheerios, 2011 (Box 119, Folder 9)
    - 6/27--Perdue Farms, 2011 (Box 119, Folder 10)
    - 7/7--Cover Girl, 2011 (Box 119, Folder 11)
    - 7/7--MasterCard "Priceless", 2011 (Box 119, Folder 12)
    - 7/8--7-Eleven, 2011 (Box 119, Folder 13)
    - 7/8--Geico, 2011 (Box 119, Folder 14)
    - 7/11--AOL/Publishers Clearing House, 2011 (Box 119, Folder 15)
    - 7/11--Derek Jeter 3000th hit, 2011 (Box 119, Folder 16)
    - 7/11--Got Milk? PMS ads, 2011 (Box 120, Folder 1)
    - 7/12--ZO Forecast (Zenith Optimedia), 2011 (Box 120, Folder 2)
    - 7/15--Google Book, 2011 (Box 120, Folder 3)
    - 7/15--MSL Group, 2011 (Box 120, Folder 4)
    - 7/15--South Park, 2011 (Box 120, Folder 5)
    - 7/18--Monterey Bay Aquarium, 2011 (Box 120, Folder 6)
    - 7/18--Ogilvy Culture, 2011 (Box 120, Folder 7)
    - 7/19--Back to School, 2011 (Box 120, Folder 8)
    - 7/19--LGBT Brands, 2011 (Box 120, Folder 9)
    - 7/20--McDonald's, 2011 (Box 120, Folder 10)
    - 7/21--Milk Board PMS campaign, 2011 (Box 120, Folder 11)
    - 7/22--CVS, 2011 (Box 120, Folder 12)
    - 7/22--Lucky Style Collective, 2011 (Box 120, Folder 13)
    - 7/25--Arts, 2011 (Box 120, Folder 14)
    - 7/25--LG, 2011 (Box 121, Folder 1)
    - 7/25--Red Lobster, 2011 (Box 121, Folder 2)
    - 7/26--Xinhua, 2011 (Box 121, Folder 3)
    - 8/16--DraftFCB layoffs, 2011 (Box 121, Folder 4)
    - 8/16--Facebook/Interpublic, 2011 (Box 121, Folder 5)
    - 8/17--Common/Alex Bogusky, 2011 (Box 121, Folder 6)
    - 8/18--Dunkin' Donuts, 2011 (Box 121, Folder 7)
    - 8/19--Amalgamated/Brian Martin, 2011 (Box 121, Folder 8)
    - 8/22--Bing/Glee (series), 2011 (Box 121, Folder 9)
    - 8/22--Mad Men (series), 2011 (Box 121, Folder 10)
    - 8/22--Recycle Bank, 2011 (Box 121, Folder 11)
    - 8/22--Tom Morton/Euro RSCG, 2011 (Box 121, Folder 12)
    - 8/23--Glee (series)/Fashion Night Out, 2011 (Box 121, Folder 13)
    - 8/23--GM media review, 2011 (Box 121, Folder 14)
    - 8/24--Ad Council, 2011 (Box 121, Folder 15)
    - 8/24--Mountain Dew, 2011 (Box 121, Folder 16)
    - 8/25--Kemper/Unitrin, 2011 (Box 121, Folder 17)
    - 8/25--NFL Fantasy Draft, 2011 (Box 121, Folder 18)
    - 8/25--Steve Jobs/Apple, 2011 (Box 121, Folder 19)
    - 8/26--BMW, 2011 (Box 121, Folder 20)
    - 8/29--[yellow tail] winery, 2011 (Box 121, Folder 21)
    - 8/30--Hurricane Irene, 2011 (Box 122, Folder 1)
    - 8/31--Honest Tea, 2011 (Box 122, Folder 2)
    - 9/1--9/11 10th anniversary, 2011; 2 folders (Box 122, Folder 3-4)
    - 9/2--PETA/Cloris Leachman, 2011 (Box 122, Folder 5)
    - 9/6--RT French, 2011 (Box 122, Folder 6)
    - 9/6--Uniqlo, 2011; 2 folders (Box 122, Folder 7-8)
    - 9/6--Verizon/Communications Workers of America 9/11 ads, 2011 (Box 122, Folder 9)
    - 9/7--Univision advertising, 2011 (Box 122, Folder 10)
    - 9/8--FedEx, 2011 (Box 122, Folder 11)
    - 9/8--VW Beetle, 2011 (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - 9/8--Yahoo!, 2011 (Box 123, Folder 2)
    - 9/9--Jobs Plan, 2011 (Box 123, Folder 3)
    - 9/9--Barbarian Group, 2011 (Box 123, Folder 4)
    - 9/11--Social media, 2011 (Box 123, Folder 5)
    - 9/12--AXA Equitable online game, 2011 (Box 123, Folder 6)
    - 9/12--Kantar/Ad spending, 2011 (Box 123, Folder 7)
    - 9/12--Knorr, 2011 (Box 123, Folder 8)
    - 9/13--Smith Wollensky, 2011 (Box 123, Folder 9)
    - 9/14--9/11-themed ads 10th anniversary, 2011 (Box 123, Folder 10)
    - 9/14--Holiday seasons, 2011 (Box 123, Folder 11)
    - 9/14--Ritz-Carlton hotels, 2011 (Box 123, Folder 12)
    - 9/15--Clorox, 2011 (Box 123, Folder 13)
    - 9/16--Ameriprise, 2011 (Box 123, Folder 14)
    - 9/16--Coke/Happiness Factory, 2011 (Box 123, Folder 15)
    - 9/16--Fleisher's Grass Fed Organic Meats, 2011 (Box 123, Folder 16)
    - 9/16--MDC Partners/Concentric/Laird, 2011 (Box 123, Folder 17)
    - 9/16--Smart Car, 2011 (Box 123, Folder 18)
    - 9/19--Brooklyn Academy of Music (BAM), 2011 (Box 123, Folder 19)
    - 9/21--Grey Healthy People, 2011 (Box 123, Folder 20)
    - 9/22--Honda/Jason Bateman, 2011 (Box 124, Folder 1)
    - 9/22--Jagermeister, 2011 (Box 124, Folder 2)
    - 9/26--Boston University, 2011 (Box 124, Folder 3)
    - 9/26--Wendy's, 2011 (Box 124, Folder 4)
    - 9/27--New York Writes Itself, 2011 (Box 124, Folder 5)
    - 9/28--Google/Nielsen, 2011 (Box 124, Folder 6)
    - 9/29--Marketing to Moms, 2011 (Box 124, Folder 7)
    - 9/30--Direct Marketing Association, 2011 (Box 124, Folder 8)
    - 10/3--Advertising Week, 2011 (Box 124, Folder 9)
    - 10/3--SyFy Channel/Halloween, 2011 (Box 124, Folder 10)
    - 10/3--Ultimat vodka, 2011 (Box 124, Folder 11)
    - 10/4--Advertising Week, 2011 (Box 124, Folder 12)
    - 10/5--Advertising Week, 2011 (Box 124, Folder 13)
    - 10/6--Advertising Week, 2011 (Box 124, Folder 14)
    - 10/7--Advertising Week, 2011 (Box 124, Folder 15)
    - 10/7--TBWA/Apple, 2011 (Box 124, Folder 16)
    - 10/10--Advertising Week, 2011 (Box 125, Folder 1)
    - 10/10--Hilton Garden Inn/United Airlines, 2011 (Box 125, Folder 2)
    - 10/11--Gate/Carrafiello-Diehl, 2011 (Box 125, Folder 3)
    - 10/11--Jomar, 2011 (Box 125, Folder 4)
    - 10/11--Popular Mechanics, 2011 (Box 125, Folder 5)
    - 10/12--Kwittken/Epoch, 2011 (Box 125, Folder 6)
    - 10/13--General Mills/DC Comics, 2011 (Box 125, Folder 7)
    - 10/13--Toyota Camry, 2011 (Box 125, Folder 8)
    - 10/14--Euro RSCG, 2011 (Box 125, Folder 9)
    - 10/17--Five Point Snacks, 2011 (Box 125, Folder 10)
    - 10/17--Marie Claire, 2011 (Box 125, Folder 11)
    - 10/17--Michael Wolff/Adweek, 2011 (Box 125, Folder 12)
    - 10/19--Chevrolet 100th anniversary, 2011 (Box 125, Folder 13)
    - 10/19--Glad/Clorox, 2011 (Box 125, Folder 14)
    - 10/21--ANA Conference, 2011 (Box 125, Folder 15)
    - 10/23--Chevrolet, 2011 (Box 125, Folder 16)
    - 10/24--ANA Conference, 2011 (Box 126, Folder 1)
    - 10/25--ANA Conference, 2011 (Box 126, Folder 2)
    - 10/27--Absolut LGBT, 2011 (Box 126, Folder 3)
    - 10/28--ESPN Deportes, 2011 (Box 126, Folder 4)
    - 10/28--Toys R Us Christmas, 2011 (Box 126, Folder 5)
    - 10/31--WQXR, 2011 (Box 126, Folder 6)
    - 11/1--American Heritage Dictionary, 2011 (Box 126, Folder 7)
    - 11/2--LG TV, 2011 (Box 126, Folder 8)
    - 11/3--Mexico Taxi Project, 2011 (Box 126, Folder 9)
    - 11/7--Brand USA, 2011 (Box 126, Folder 10)
    - 11/7--Owner IQ, 2011 (Box 126, Folder 11)
    - 11/7--Schwab, 2011 (Box 126, Folder 12)
    - 11/7--Sun Valley, 2011 (Box 126, Folder 13)
    - 11/7--Visa Facebook, 2011 (Box 126, Folder 14)
    - 11/8--JC Penney Christmas, 2011 (Box 126, Folder 15)
    - 11/9--Veteran's Day, 2011 (Box 127, Folder 1)
    - 11/10--11/11/11, 2011 (Box 127, Folder 2)
    - 11/11--Kraft Belvita, 2011 (Box 127, Folder 3)
    - 11/11--Humor in ads, 2011 (Box 127, Folder 4)
    - 11/11--Vitro/Skinny, 2011 (Box 127, Folder 5)
    - 11/13--TNT/Hyatt, 2011 (Box 127, Folder 6)
    - 11/15--Agency executives, 2011 (Box 127, Folder 7)
    - 11/15--AXA Equitable, 2011 (Box 127, Folder 8)
    - 11/15--JC Penney, 2011 (Box 127, Folder 9)
    - 11/15--Target Christmas, 2011 (Box 127, Folder 10)
    - 11/15--TV advertising market, 2011 (Box 127, Folder 11)
    - 11/17--Accenture, 2011 (Box 127, Folder 12)
    - 11/17--Smirnoff, 2011 (Box 127, Folder 13)
    - 11/18--Betty Crocker, 2011 (Box 127, Folder 14)
    - 11/21--Progressive Insurance, 2011 (Box 127, Folder 15)
    - 11/21--Public Relations Society of America, 2011 (Box 128, Folder 1)
    - 11/21--Vicks Vapodad, 2011 (Box 128, Folder 2)
    - 11/23--Brand Investment, 2011 (Box 128, Folder 3)
    - 11/23--Lincoln Financial, 2011 (Box 128, Folder 4)
    - 11/23--Wodka billboard, 2011 (Box 128, Folder 5)
    - 11/25--Google GoMo, 2011 (Box 128, Folder 6)
    - 11/25--Jingle Punks Hipster Orchestra, 2011 (Box 128, Folder 7)
    - 11/28--20 Questions, 2011 (Box 128, Folder 8)
    - 11/28--Norton/Symantec, 2011 (Box 128, Folder 9)
    - 11/28--Southern Comfort, 2011 (Box 128, Folder 10)
    - 11/29--McGruff/Counterfeiting, 2011 (Box 128, Folder 11)
    - 11/29--Western Union, 2011 (Box 128, Folder 12)
    - 12/1--MDC/Anne Bologna, 2011 (Box 128, Folder 13)
    - 12/5--Young Rubicam, 2011 (Box 128, Folder 14)
    - 12/7--2012 forecast, 2011 (Box 129, Folder 1)
    - 12/9--Travel ads, 2011 (Box 129, Folder 2)
    - 12/10--Trademark auction, 2011 (Box 129, Folder 3)
    - 12/12--Cheil, 2011 (Box 129, Folder 4)
    - 12/12--Royal Caribbean, 2011 (Box 129, Folder 5)
    - 12/13--All American Muslim, 2011 (Box 129, Folder 6)
    - 12/14--Clearasil, 2011 (Box 129, Folder 7)
    - 12/14--Kayak/All American Muslim, 2011 (Box 129, Folder 8)
    - 12/14--Young Rubicam/Suzanne Hart, 2011 (Box 129, Folder 9)
    - 12/15--State Farm, 2011 (Box 129, Folder 10)
    - 12/16--Lincoln, 2011 (Box 129, Folder 11)
    - 12/16--Pop-up stores, 2011 (Box 129, Folder 12)
    - 12/16--Young Rubicam Reunion, 2011 (Box 129, Folder 13)
    - 12/19--Best and worst advertising, 2011 (Box 129, Folder 14)
    - 12/19--Kantar/Ad spending, 2011 (Box 130, Folder 1)
    - 12/23--Year in media, 2011 (Box 130, Folder 2)
    - Super Bowl, 2011 (Box 130, Folder 3)
    - Super Bowl--20th Century Fox, 2011 (Box 130, Folder 4)
    - Super Bowl--Anheuser-Busch, 2011 (Box 130, Folder 5)
    - Super Bowl--Audi, 2011 (Box 130, Folder 6)
    - Super Bowl--Best Buy, 2011 (Box 130, Folder 7)
    - Super Bowl--BMW/Mini, 2011 (Box 130, Folder 8)
    - Super Bowl--Bridgestone, 2011 (Box 130, Folder 9)
    - Super Bowl--CareerBuilder, 2011 (Box 130, Folder 10)
    - Super Bowl--CarMax, 2011 (Box 130, Folder 11)
    - Super Bowl--Cars.com, 2011 (Box 130, Folder 12)
    - Super Bowl--Chevrolet, 2011 (Box 130, Folder 13)
    - Super Bowl--Chrysler, 2011 (Box 130, Folder 14)
    - Super Bowl--Coca-Cola, 2011 (Box 130, Folder 15)
    - Super Bowl--E*Trade, 2011 (Box 130, Folder 16)
    - Super Bowl--GoDaddy.com, 2011 (Box 130, Folder 17)
    - Super Bowl--HomeAway, 2011 (Box 130, Folder 18)
    - Super Bowl--Hyundai, 2011 (Box 130, Folder 19)
    - Super Bowl--Kia, 2011 (Box 130, Folder 20)
    - Super Bowl--Mercedes, 2011 (Box 130, Folder 21)
    - Super Bowl--Motorola, 2011 (Box 130, Folder 22)
    - Super Bowl--NFL, 2011 (Box 130, Folder 23)
    - Super Bowl--Paramount, 2011 (Box 130, Folder 24)
    - Super Bowl--Pepsi/Doritos, 2011 (Box 130, Folder 25)
    - Super Bowl--Skechers, 2011 (Box 130, Folder 26)
    - Super Bowl--Snickers, 2011 (Box 130, Folder 27)
    - Super Bowl--Sony Ericsson, 2011 (Box 130, Folder 28)
    - Super Bowl--Teleflora, 2011 (Box 130, Folder 29)
    - Super Bowl--VW, 2011 (Box 130, Folder 30)
  - 2012, 7
    - 1/5--R.J. Palmer/MDC Partners, 2012 (Box 130, Folder 31)
    - 1/6--Dr. Pepper, 2012 (Box 130, Folder 32)
    - 1/9--Brita/Univision, 2012 (Box 130, Folder 33)
    - 1/9--Corbis/Norm Marshall, 2012 (Box 130, Folder 34)
    - 1/10--Magazine advertising, 2012 (Box 130, Folder 35)
    - 1/11--Bank of America/Chase Sapphire, 2012 (Box 130, Folder 36)
    - 1/11--Bill Cella, 2012 (Box 130, Folder 37)
    - 1/11--Super Bowl/Honda, 2012 (Box 131, Folder 1)
    - 1/12--Target/Apple, 2012 (Box 131, Folder 2)
    - 1/13--NBC/Nike, 2012 (Box 131, Folder 3)
    - 1/13--Nostalgia in advertising (Starkist, Pine Bros., Dr. Pepper, Planters), 2012 (Box 131, Folder 4)
    - 1/13--Procter Gamble Olympics "Thank You Mom", 2012 (Box 131, Folder 5)
    - 1/17--Uncle Ben's, 2012 (Box 131, Folder 6)
    - 1/18--Kraft, 2012 (Box 131, Folder 7)
    - 1/19--Super Bowl/Dannon, 2012 (Box 131, Folder 8)
    - 1/20--Bing, 2012 (Box 131, Folder 9)
    - 1/23--ANA Alliance for Family Entertainment, 2012 (Box 131, Folder 10)
    - 1/23--Huntington Helps.com, 2012 (Box 131, Folder 11)
    - 1/24--General Motors, 2012 (Box 131, Folder 12)
    - 1/25--JC Penney, 2012 (Box 131, Folder 13)
    - 1/26--Hawaii Tourism, 2012 (Box 132, Folder 1)
    - 1/30--Curve Appeal/Liz Claiborne, 2012 (Box 132, Folder 2)
    - 1/30--Tabasco/Reckitt Benckiser, 2012 (Box 132, Folder 3)
    - 1/31--Time Warner Cable, 2012 (Box 132, Folder 4)
    - 2/2--Super Bowl/Shazzam, 2012 (Box 132, Folder 5)
    - 2/3--Super Bowl preview, 2012 (Box 132, Folder 6)
    - 2/6--Global Association of Risk Professionals, 2012 (Box 132, Folder 7)
    - 2/6--Super Bowl review, 2012 (Box 132, Folder 8)
    - 2/7--Super Bowl recap, 2012 (Box 132, Folder 9)
    - 2/8--Super Bowl/Facebook, 2012 (Box 132, Folder 10)
    - 2/8--Target/NickMom, 2012 (Box 132, Folder 11)
    - 2/10--Recipe to Riches, 2012 (Box 133, Folder 1)
    - 2/10--Super Bowl/Chevrolet, 2012 (Box 133, Folder 2)
    - 2/13--Social@Ogilvy, 2012 (Box 133, Folder 3)
    - 2/13--UCLA, 2012 (Box 133, Folder 4)
    - 2/15--Coca-Cola/Olympics, 2012 (Box 133, Folder 5)
    - 2/15--Tide Pods, 2012 (Box 133, Folder 6)
    - 2/15--Travel Channel, 2012 (Box 133, Folder 7)
    - 2/16--Made in America, 2012 (Box 133, Folder 8)
    - 2/17--ANA TV Forum, 2012 (Box 133, Folder 9)
    - 2/17--Dentsu/Publicis, 2012 (Box 133, Folder 10)
    - 2/21--Ad spending, 2012 (Box 133, Folder 11)
    - 2/21--BBC America, 2012 (Box 133, Folder 12)
    - 2/21--National CineMedia, 2012 (Box 133, Folder 13)
    - 2/22--Canoe, 2012 (Box 133, Folder 14)
    - 2/22--Team Enterprises/Shopper marketing, 2012 (Box 133, Folder 15)
    - 2/24--Academy Awards (Oscars), 2012 (Box 133, Folder 16)
    - 2/24--NASCAR, 2012 (Box 134, Folder 1)
    - 2/24--OMD/Hackathon, 2012 (Box 134, Folder 2)
    - 2/27--Mad Men (series), 2012 (Box 134, Folder 3)
    - 2/27--Renuzit, 2012 (Box 134, Folder 4)
    - 2/28--Oreo 100th anniversary, 2012 (Box 134, Folder 5)
    - 2/28--Product of the Year Awards, 2012 (Box 134, Folder 6)
    - 2/29--A. Eicoff, 2012 (Box 134, Folder 7)
    - 2/29--Bravo/Chase, 2012 (Box 134, Folder 8)
    - 2/29--Cheezburger, 2012 (Box 134, Folder 9)
    - 3/1--Applebee's, 2012 (Box 134, Folder 10)
    - 3/2--Public Relations Defined, 2012 (Box 134, Folder 11)
    - 3/5--Coldwell Banker, 2012 (Box 134, Folder 12)
    - 3/5--Scotts, 2012 (Box 134, Folder 13)
    - 3/6--Mad Men era, 2012 (Box 134, Folder 14)
    - 3/7--Self Magazine, 2012 (Box 134, Folder 15)
    - 3/9--Google, 2012 (Box 135, Folder 1)
    - 3/12--Method (brand), 2012 (Box 135, Folder 2)
    - 3/12--Omnicom/Terry Young, 2012 (Box 135, Folder 3)
    - 3/13--Volkswagen, 2012 (Box 135, Folder 4)
    - 3/13--Zenith Optimedia forecast, 2012 (Box 135, Folder 5)
    - 3/14--Disney Channel upfront, 2012 (Box 135, Folder 6)
    - 3/15--ANA/WFA Global Marketing Conference, 2012 (Box 135, Folder 7)
    - 3/16--GEICO/Gecko America campaign, 2012 (Box 135, Folder 8)
    - 3/19--Google GoMo, 2012 (Box 135, Folder 9)
    - 3/19--Hennessey, 2012 (Box 135, Folder 10)
    - 3/19--Mad Men season 5, 2012 (Box 135, Folder 11)
    - 3/20--ESPN, 2012 (Box 135, Folder 12)
    - 3/20--TargetCast/MDC Partners, 2012 (Box 135, Folder 13)
    - 3/21--AMC "The Pitch" (series), 2012 (Box 135, Folder 14)
    - 3/21--Game Show Network, 2012 (Box 136, Folder 1)
    - 3/23--Greek Tourism, 2012 (Box 136, Folder 2)
    - 3/23--Nissan "Taxi of Tomorrow", 2012 (Box 136, Folder 3)
    - 3/26--AAAA Open Advertising, 2012 (Box 136, Folder 4)
    - 3/26--TNT/Dallas (series), 2012 (Box 136, Folder 5)
    - 4/2--AAAA (American Association of Advertising Agencies), 2012 (Box 136, Folder 6)
    - 4/3--Bacardi, 2012 (Box 136, Folder 7)
    - 4/3--Havas, 2012 (Box 136, Folder 8)
    - 4/3--Weather Channel upfront, 2012 (Box 136, Folder 8a)
    - 4/4--Doner, 2012 (Box 136, Folder 9)
    - 4/5--Funny or Die, 2012 (Box 136, Folder 10)
    - 4/9--AT, 2012 (Box 136, Folder 11)
    - 4/9--My Dirty Jobs, 2012 (Box 136, Folder 12)
    - 4/10--Motel 6, 2012 (Box 136, Folder 13)
    - 4/11--EcoMedia, 2012 (Box 137, Folder 1)
    - 4/13--Google Brief update, 2012 (Box 137, Folder 2)
    - 4/13--Titanic, 2012 (Box 137, Folder 3)
    - 4/16--Reading is Fundamental campaign, 2012 (Box 137, Folder 4)
    - 4/19--Generation Y/NBCUniversal, 2012 (Box 137, Folder 5)
    - 4/23--Moscot, 2012 (Box 137, Folder 6)
    - 4/25--Magic Johnson/Aspire, 2012 (Box 137, Folder 7)